Gary Fisher Papers, 1973-1997 GLC 51
James C. Hormel Gay & Lesbian Center, San Francisco Public Library
Gary Fisher Papers,
1973-1997
1980-1994
GLC 51
Fisher, Gary, 1961-1994
3.5 boxes (3.5 cubic feet)
James C. Hormel Gay & Lesbian Center, San Francisco Public Library 100 Larkin Street San Francisco, CA, 94102 (415) 557-4400 info@sfpl.org
The collection contains the notebooks, diaries, journals, poems and short fiction of Gary Fisher, a gay African American man. It also includes the transcripts and excerpts used for Gary in Your Pocket, edited by Eve Kosofsky Sedgwick.
Access
The collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Gary Fisher Papers were donated to the San Francisco Public Library in 1998 by Eve Kosofsky Sedgwick, the literary executor of the Gary Fisher Estate.
Biographical note
Gary Fisher was a gay African American man who enjoyed writing and drawing and was a dedicated diarist. He was born on June 19, 1961 in Bristol, Pennsylvania. Fisher attended the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill from 1979-1983 and studied English and creative writing. He died of AIDS at the age of 32 on February 22, 1994. After his death, Eve Kosofsky Sedgwick edited portions of his journals, poems and stories in order to publish Gary in Your Pocket. Sedwick includes a full biography of Fisher at the end of Gary in Your Pocket.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes the written work, journals and drawings of Gary Fisher. It also includes the files created by Eve Kosofsky Sedgwick as she edited Fisher's work for the publication of Gary in Your Pocket. There is a small amount of correspondence and photographs.
Arrangement note
The papers have been arranged into six series: Series 1. Notebooks; Series 2. Journals / Diaries; Series 3. Poems, Short Fiction, and Other Writing; Series 4. Gary in Your Pocket Files; Series 5. Correspondence; and, Series 6. Printed Materials.
Fisher, Gary, 1961-1994--Archives; Sedgwick, Eve Kosofsky; African-American authors--Archives; African-American gay men--Archives; Gay men's writings--United States; Gay men--California--San Francisco--Diaries; Gay men--California--San Francisco--Social life and customs--20th century; Gay men--United States--Diaries; Gay poetry--United States
- Notebooks, 1980-1994; Series 1; 28.0 folders + 1 oversized folder
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains Fisher's class notebooks, and includes notes and drafts of stories and poems that he developed later. There are some interesting drawings in conte crayon and pastels as well. Occasionally there are journal-style entries on his day-to-day activities and health. Sedgwick provided descriptions of many of the notebooks.
  Arrangement note
  Arranged by number with unnumbered notebooks filed at the beginning.
  - Notebooks. Transcriptions [Gary in Your Pocket?], undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Notebook. "Kitchie Stuff,", undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    General note
    Tawny is a character in the story.
  - Notebook, March 15, 1989-April 22, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Notebook 1, January 1989?- January 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    "Light-blue bound composition book. Year 1989 appears on p. 24. Numbered pages (by printer). First page dated 1/28. Teaching notes. Story beginning 'On Sundays our mother unleashed energies...' being drafted and redrafted pages 13-21. A dream on p.23. Pages 27-35, notes and journal from a trip east. Date 1/31/92 appears on p. 35. Blank after p.35."--EKS
  - Notebook 2, April 30-May 1, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    "Mead marbled bound composition book (black and white). First page dated 4/30/93. 8 or 9 pages of hospital journal (that I don't remember reading elsewhere). Six loose sheets of long manila, written with notes for, and drafts of paragraphs of, a story about Marshall and a gun. Four long manila pages, loose, of a story called 'Mr. Maddox's Face.'"--EKS
  - Notebook 3. "Music,", undated (Box 1, Folder 6, Oversize-folder 1)
    "Blue, bound composition book. Cover says 'Music.' 4 written pages and many loose manila long pages of music lists."--EKS
  - Notebook 4, September 12-November 2, 19-- (Box 1, Folder 7)
    "3-inch x 5-inch red notebook, spiral bound at top, labeled 'ideas...' Random notes, undated, including some little anecdotes, teaching notes, shopping lists, etc."--EKS
  - Notebook 5, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folders 8-9)
    "Peacock blue two-ring looseleaf binder. Cellophane pocket on front says 'Fisher.' Copies and drafts of poems, dated 1980-1985. Four poems loose."--EKS. Pages removed from binder.
  - Notebook 6. "Ideas,", 1988-January 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    "White speckled ring-bound notebook, circa 5-inches x 7-inches; front cover says 'ideas.' Random notes, including many notes for/about stories (e.g. about the idea of 'Red Cream Soda.') Undated till late, but seems to begin during spring 1987 (includes notes from my class, some things later included in class journal). Little vignettes; graffiti."--EKS
  - Notebook 7, January 11-April 30, 1992, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    "Bound notebook, buff, unbleached cover, 6-inches x 7-inches. First date 1/11/92; last date 4/30/92. 13 pages of entries. Mostly re: illness, living and dying. Notes for a zine."--EKS
  - Notebook 8, July 3-August 23, 1993, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    "Unbleached corrugated notebook bound with string, 4-inches x 5-inches. Hospital and related notes, seemingly from 6-7/93."--EKS
  - Notebook [9], May 18-September 10, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    "Unbleached textured string-bound notebook, 5-inches x 7-1/2-inches. Hospital notebook, 5/18/93-9/10/93. A few pen and pencil drawings (mostly landscapes)."--EKS
  - Notebook [10], June 30, 1993-January 13, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    "Unbleached corrugated notebook bound with string, 8-1/2-inches x 11-inches. Entries dated 6/30/93-10/18/93. Color and b/w drawings, by Gary and others."--EKS
  - Notebook 11, January-February 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    "Folio diary 1994, yellow and green print paper binding, 6-7 entries."--EKS
  - Notebook 12 "Chaucer,", Fall 1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    "Blue paper binding, course notes, Fall '87 with syllabus and handouts, and loose page of notes with paragraph of story in blue ink, also notes on medieval and renaissance authors."--EKS
  - Notebook 13 "Shakespeare,", Fall 1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    "Blue paper binding, 8/27-, Joel Feinman Fall '87 course notes, with syllabus, loose leaves, notes, handouts, [notes in square brackets may be Gary's miscellaneous commentaries]."--EKS
  - Notebook 14 "Fiction,", 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    "Fiction: September (24) 1984 Blue spiral bound CAI notebook, half full: notes for and on 'Villains of Necessity' with poem and story critique, notes for other works: Radioman, Tawny, At Other People's Parties. 9/4/85 notes for Breslin's American Poetry. Notes for story: Twelve. To do list."--EKS
  - Notebook 15 "Sundquist, etc.,", undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    "Bound composition notebook, three quarters full, blue paper binding, February (Spring) course notes on ethnic and women's literature, some drawings and verse, paragraphs for papers on 'Bennito Cerino' and Chaucer and Christine de Pisan."--EKS
  - Notebook 16 [Poetry, etc. by Fisher], 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    "Turquoise blue spiral notebook, poems and lyrics from 6/24, 1980 clear copies with some revisions, paginated to 33, same format to p.35; notes on characters, lyrics, notes for fiction, loose leaves from German school work[?]: poem 'Without' 9/14/81, essay on Death of a Salesman, essay on Greek drama."--EKS
  - Notebook 17 "English 58" [Shakespeare], Spring 19-- (Box 1, Folder 21)
    "Tan spiral UNC notebook, Spring 19--, notes on Shakespeare course; with essays on Othello and Keats, theme of excess in Jane Eyre, Frankenstein, and Tenant of Wildfell Hall, one page poem, random notes, including song lists."--EKS
  - Notebook 18, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    General ntoe
    "Red UNC spiral notebook: notes for Bug, Tawny; 'Going to California Sale' notice, record lists, poem starts, notes and paper draft on To the Lighthouse; paper on O'Connor's 'Revelation;' poem 'Outside'—long narrative poem with dialogue. Typescript of Tawny's radio story, and 'Prayer.'"--EKS
  - Notebook 19 "English 35P,", Spring 1983 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    "William Harmon, Tan UNC spiral notebook, Poetics class notes with literature terms, and loose leaves of course notes. Loose leaf notes: prostitutes, quote from John Berger…handouts, draft of paper on Dano-Norwegan."--EKS
  - Notebook 20 "Shakespeare / Richmond,", Fall 1988 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    "Green pebble paper bound notebook, AF-AM1B course notes, notes for story based on racialized Midsummernight's Dream; a memory, 2-5 Nellie (sophomore); list of students' papers and grades. Loose half sheet yellow, course notes, [brackets for story notes]; notes for African American Literature for teaching; more TA notes."--EKS
  - Notebook [21] "Sedgwick,", Spring 1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    "Blue bound composition book, notes from gay/lesbian studies course."--EKS
  - Notebook [22] "Notes, Dykes to Watch Out For,", [1989]-1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    "Bound blue composition book. Dykes to Watch Out For strips pasted onto many pages; 3 loose strips. First date is 10/10 (89?); last date is 4/10/90. Journal and writing draft entries including 'Coupons;' lecture notes; a poem."--EKS
  - Notebook 23 "Breslin,", Fall 1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    "Tan UC spiral-bound notebook. First date 8/28/85. Class notes from Breslin class (20th C. American poetry?). 8 pp. loose notes on class. A couple of journal-like entries, a draft letter, toward end of notebook."--EKS
  - Notebook 24 "Modernism (203),", Spring 1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    "Tan spiral-bound 'made especially for the asuc store' notebook. First date 1/22/85. Class notes from Breslin 'Modernism' course (Spring 85). Many loose pages on back of green forms; 3 pads of green forms with writing on backs of forms; other loose pages. Some poems and ephemera in notebook and (especially) on loose pp."--EKS
- Journals / Diaries, 1977-1993; Series 2; 18.0 folders
  This series documents Fisher's activities and thoughts as an African-American gay man. The journals include everything from ticket stubs for events he attended, to copies of the sex ads he placed in gay magazines and newspapers. It also includes drawings, some notes on poems, and stories. Ephemera from Journals I-XI was separated and appears in Box 4 / Folders 1-2. Sedgwick provided descriptions of many of the journals. The series contains some correspondence.
  Arranged chronologically by journal number. Unnumbered journals and drawing tablets appear after the initial chronological sequence.
  - Journal I, September 3, 1977-December 31, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    "Orange spiral bound Euro format, Gary Fisher in plastic tape type in grey on cover; pages numbered through 79; written Germany and Virginia, USA. Stapled in letter, TV Guide notes, other memorabilia."--EKS
  - Journal II, January-December 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    "4-inch x 6-inch yellow box, brocade bound diary with Gary's calling card on opening endsheet. 1/1/79, pages numbered to 267. Ends with New Year's resolutions for 1980; loose leaf of invite to Junior Senior prom, taped in; song lists; stapled in ticket stub, tipped in Oscar list; tipped in TV Guide pictures; page 107 taped over, 'You'll never know.'"--EKS
  - Journal III, January 1, 1980-January 14, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    "Pages numbered to 210; black bound 'blank book,' with spine missing; in Phoenix; BeeGees lyrics paper clipped in; note taped in; cartoons taped in; drawings; 4/13/80 journal supplement, paper clipped in; page 133 song lyric; pages 146-147 poetry; football team pictures tipped in; page 157 taped in letter in response to personals ad; page 161 taped in note; Elephant Man program tipped in; pages 188-190 poetry; Dan Fogleberg lyrics tipped in; page 197 greeting card; end phrases and notes and song lists on unnumbered pages."--EKS
  - Journal IV, January 16-November 13, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    "Black bound 'blank book' pages numbered to 167, unnumbered continue. UNC. Marven.; [page] 29 Valentines card; [pages] 40-- letters to self; [page] 47 annotated poem; [page] 93 tipped in parent's business card; [page] 96 theater ticket; [page] 113 Christmas card; [page] 116 birthday cards; [page] 128 letter from Leslie; [page] 162 draft note clipped in; titled work in unnumbered pages at end."--EKS
  - Journal V, November 15, 1981-October 4, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    "Black bound 'blank book' unnumbered pages, some passages highlighted; loose leaves; letter to Jack xerox, notes; small square cut sheets tipped in, poems; xerox of letter to Ray; 3 letters from Ray; invitation to Donna's college graduation; Rex Reed article; poem; draft of letters clipped in; poems; letter from Johnny; photo; pages with post-its; letter to Charlie; letter to Charlie; record lists; letter from Jerry; xerox letter to Anita; letters from Anita; record list."--EKS
  - Journal VI, October 5, 1983-November 8, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    "'Searching' brown 'blank book;' letter from Leslie; opens with poems dated '82; notes from Susy; poems and sketches clipped in; more poems; notes about Bug; going to California; draft letter to Bill clipped in; Ritchie Bennet memorial service; letter from Mom, Dad, Luchina and Crystal and draft of poem clipped in; news clipping and two fortunes taped in; best buys 1983, records clipped in; Oscar nominations clipping taped in; note taped in ATT; birthday card from co-workers; pictures tipped in; more notes for Villains of Necessity; draft of letter (?) and page from story (?) at end tipped in."--EKS
  - Journal VII, November 9, 1984-July 21, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    "Black 'blank book' unnumbered; drawings; Franky goes to Hollywood ticket; ad tipped in; best buys '84; ballot stub; newspaper clipping; Ballet de Troc. Program; poem on 'while writing term papers' 4/20/82; letter to Mr. Blackmail personals; newsclippings, card from Don; symphony ticket; top 40; notes taped in; poem/lyric tipped in; three IDs taped in; four green pages journal supplement tipped in; address taped in; letter to mother on parchment 12/27/85; favorite records '85; personal ad response; 'Dear Mr. Hunk' two pages yellow ruled; stop AIDS project flyers; NCAA and other clippings; apt. hunting; hashbrown and top ten lists; Lily Tomlin concert, New York Matsuda; notes on cut sheets; Merchant of Venice program; Mother at Duke Med Center; ticket to new York."--EKS
  - Journal VIII, July 24, 1986-December 11, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    "Black bound; opens with pastel drawing; record list; wine label; note tipped in; story notes; Midsummer Mozart program; yellow ruled sheet of journal 1/14/87; clippings; birthday card; Paul Simon tickets; cartoons; sex ad; dick survey on back of xerox; personal ads; program with note on it; note from Eric Sundquist; invitation to Eve's party; letter to Marvin; election flyer; phone number; letter to Jan; Faulkner stamp; wine labels; personal ads; card; Anita Baker ticket; cartoons (Calvin & Hobbes); card from Scott Hamm; printout of 10/31/87 journal entry; letter to Gary, response to ad; letter Pete 3/26/88; picture of NC writing teacher; Leontyne Price program, clipping, and ticket; David Schiff program 5/88 with journal notes; Fag Club flyer with notes on back; responses to personals ads; 7/6 & 9/88 extra journal entries, printouts; letter to Gary; Midnight Run ticket; post-it; bus. card; letter from Leslie 4/17/88; taped shut envelope; letters for ads yellow sheets; ends with Calvin and Hobbes and list of movies and opinions."--EKS
  - Journal IX, March 19, 1989-December 17, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    "White bound book; 3 pages of yellow pad, letter to STH; phone number on paper tipped in; draft of letter to 'Dear Northern Italian Man'; hospital bracelet; Field of Dreams review; personals ad; Soul Survivor flyer; personals ad; letter to Marvin; ticket to Urinal; note taped in, vignette; the Slave's Creed; clipping and top 40 list; assignation note; calendar pages; Prince tix."--EKS
  - Journal X, December 31, 1990-April 25, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    "Blue and black with cloth in photo collage cover papers; 2 columns, loose sheets tan and yellow; New Years Resolutions '91; won contest !; clipping; clipping; bus. card and loose cut sheet note."--EKS
  - Journal XI, March 10, 1990-March 23, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    "Page cut out at beginning, undated pages, black bound with Moorish tile paper covers; first dated Fri 3/10/90, 7/23/90, 7/20/90, 7/31/90, 8/22, 29; 9/2/90; 3/23/91; rest blank."--EKS
  - Ephemera from Journals I-XI (arranged in by journal number). "Includes important stuff--letters, drafts, journal material,", 1978-1990 (Box 4, Folders 1-2)
  - Journal [unnumbered], September 21, 1989-February 6, [1990?] (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Small notebook, 1991, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Utility sketchbook, 1991, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Journal Drawings, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Sketch pad with pastel drawings, 1993, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Poems, Short Fiction, and Other Writing, 1973-1994; Series 3; 56.0 folders
  This series contains drafts and final copy of short fiction and poems written by Fisher. Of interest are the various drafts of "Red Cream Soda," "Tawny," "The Villains of Necessity" and "Walt" which were written and re-written over several years. The earliest items in this series are a few stories from the 1970s though most of the writing is dated after 1980. The series contains some correspondence and Polaroid photographs.
  Arranged into two sections: Fiction and Other Writing. Folders within the first section are arranged alphabetically. The second section is largely arranged in original order with some additions of miscellaneous writings including the "final batch" of unsorted writings sent by Fisher's executor to Eve Kosofsky Sedgwick.
  - "After the box,", 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - "Arabesque,", 1991, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - "Barbara,", 1980 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - "Before Sleep,", 1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - "Be-ing Dead,", 1991, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - "CornerStore,", 1991, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - "Dear !", 1993 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - "Flower Lady,", undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - "Friends,", 1981 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - "Games" [also titled "Games and Polity" with character Tawny], 1993, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - "Ice Cream Talk,", 1991, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Letters, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Letters from Fisher to NEH Seminar participants, Keith Thomas, Thomas, Scott, Student Aid Office at University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, House of Representatives, and Marvin.
  - "Linda's,", undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - "Making Little Thieves,", 1994 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - "Miss Della,", 1981 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - "Mo-Day,", 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - "Mr. Madsen's Face,", 1993 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - "Penitence,", 1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - "Picarro,", 1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - "Pot Liquor,", 1993, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - "Radioland,", 1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "Red Cream Soda,", 1987-1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - "Rodney King,", 1993 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - "Sam & Newton,", 1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - "Second Virginity,", 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - "Several Lies About Mom,", 1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - "Sex,", 1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - "Tawny,", 1987-1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - "Telephone Man,", 1993, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - "Three Boys,", 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - "Twelve,", undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - "Vampire,", 1980 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - "Villains of Necessity [several drafts],", 1987-1993 (Box 3, Folders 16-17)
  - "Walking,", 1989-1993 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - "Walt,", 1988-1993 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - "Final batch" [unsorted writings, letters, Polaroid photographs], 1989-1994 (Box 4, Folders 4-6)
    Includes cover letter from Doug Sebesta, Fisher's executor, to Eve Kosofsky Sedgwick, Fisher's literary executor, 4/3/1994. Box 4 / Folder 6 includes Polaroid pictures showing some nudity and sexual content.
  - "Hospital Journal,", 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    See also:
    Box 4 / Folder 11. Correspondence to Eve Sedgwick, hospital poems, etc.
  - Miscellaneous "She could do things,", undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - "Miscellaneous" [collage, journal transcriptions], undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Box 3 / Folders 36 and 45; and Box 4 / Folder 9.
  - "In Progress," "Sonnet 5: A Necessary Failure," "The Best Book,", 1986, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - "Miscellaneous Notes," "By Force or By Freud," "Pope's Female Hero," medical bill, 1988, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Loose items: fiction, outlines, etc., 1981, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - "Bits," [includes some drafts of Tawny and Bug], undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - "Occasional," [includes Kitchie story, "Dear Mom" letter, Mr. Gates story], 1981-1986, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - "Nonsense, Waste and By-Products,", undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - "Sedgwick" [photocopies of materials about AIDS], 1987 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - "Sex Letters," and a Resolution regarding kissing, 1986-1991 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - "a Cat Poem," "c Cat Poem,", 1992 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - "Hate Poem for Jim and Others,", undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - "Poems I,", 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - "Poems II,", 1985 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - "Poems III,", 1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - "Old Stuff" includes: "Odd Ventures" (1981), "7th" (1973), "8th" "What You Can't See Can't Hurt You" "Ross" (1974), "The Gap 9th" (1975/1976), "Mania" (1980), "The Bank Robbers,", 1973-1981 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Gary In Your Pocket Files, 1977-1997; Series 4; 14.0 folders
  This series contains material related to the publication of the book Gary in Your Pocket edited by Eve Kosofsky Sedgwick. It includes transcripts of journal and notebook entries as well as correspondence with publishers, promotional material and reviews.
  Arranged alphabetically by title.
  - Journal transcriptions, 1977-1993 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Journal Transcriptions and poems, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Box 3 / Folders 21 and 45; and Box 4 / Folder 9.
  - Originals and photocopies [for Gary In Your Pocket?], 1980-1994 (Box 3, Folders 37-41)
  - Photocopies of a photograph of Gary and his sister as children, and of "Floating Penises" drawing series, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Publishing contract with Duke University for Gary In Your Pocket, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Reviews and critical response, 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - "Sedgewick Journal '87--Gary Fisher,", 1987 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    Box 3 / Folders 21 and 36; and Box 4 / Folder 9.
  - Selected poems by several poets, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Stories, 1987-1992 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    Express mail envelope with print-outs of several stories by Fisher: Arabesque (1991), Red Cream Soda, After the Box (1991), Mo-Day (1992), Cornerstore (1991), Tawny (1987). All were published in Gary in Your Pocket.
  - Stories and poems, 1985, 1992, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Box 3 / Folders 21, 36, and 45.
- Correspondence, 1982-1994; Series 5; 4.0 folders + 1 oversized folder
  The series contains correspondence between Eve Kosofsky Sedgwick and Gary Fisher, a few of Fisher's letters to some family members, and copies of some Fisher letters to Donna Ward-Kiddo. It also includes letters between Sedgwick and Karen Kelly regarding a conference talk. Additional correspondence may be found within Series 2, 3, and 4.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
  - "Letters" from Gary Fisher, and miscellaneous writing, 1985, 1993, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Letters addressed to: "Mom," "Luchina," and "Pat." Also includes notes and miscellaneous writing.
  - Between Gary Fisher and Eve Sedgwick, 1987-1994, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Box 3 / Folder 20 Hospital journal.